ASHISH SINGH

Portfolio link: https://ashishsingh8298.github.io/

**** +91 7003454270

✓ ashsihs41@gmail.com

https://github.com/ashishsingh8298

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/ashish8298/

PERSONAL DETAILS

- DOB 20th October, 1997
- Father's Name- Mr. O.P Singh
- Permanent Address- Q- II/10, KV Staff Quarter, Mughalsarai - 232101

EDUCATION

• BACHELORS OF TECHNOLOGY
(Computer Science Engineering)
NSEC Kolkata 2016-2020

• SECONDARY SCHOOL Kendriya Vidyalaya BSF Kishanganj. -2015

• HIGH SCHOOL Kendriya Vidyalaya BSF Kishanganj -2013

CORE SKILLS

- Microsoft SOL
- .NET Core Full Stack Web Development.
- Angular
- Microsoft Azure
- Azure DevOps
- MEAN Stack
- Android Development
- Programing languages:
 - C#
 - o Java
 - Python
 - o C++

OTHER SKILLS

- Leadership
- Duty Bound
- Ability to Work Under Pressure.
- Writing Skills
- Fast Learner
- Team Player

SUMMARY

Digital Specialist Engineer working on .NET core full stack Web Development. I also have knowledge and certifications in Android Developmentand MEAN Stack. I'm no stranger to hard work and my strength is I am flexible with work hours and time bound. I am always curious to learn something new.

EXPERIENCE

• Digital Specialist Engineer - Infosys

(January 2021 to Present)

- Trained on: C#, SQL Server, Entity Framework Core, ASP.NET Core Web API, Angular 9, Azure DevOps.
- Currently working for a **Client under Energy Domain**.
- Developer (Full stack) NSEC Kolkata

(April 2020 to July 2020)

Worked under Prof Sumanta Das:

- Developed Placement Success App using Android (Java).
- A Full-Fledged Web Application using HTML, CSS, Javascript, NodeJS.
- Both App and Website share common data using Firebase (NoSQL).

PROJECTS

- Yelp-Camp Web Application: Built a social media web app for camping
 enthusiasts using cutting-edge technologies like NodeJs, ExpressJs, Passport
 API, No SQL database(MongoDB).
- **Placement Success App** Build a placement app for college using Android (Java), Firebase, and hosted on GCP.

CERTIFICATIONS & ACCOMPLISHMENTS

- Cleared **Hackwithinfy** and got selected for **SES** role in Infosys.
- 3-star ranking on **Codechef**.
- Certifications in **Full-Stack Development** on Udemy.
- Certification in Python Programming language Organised by MyWBUT.
- Have solved 330+ Computer Science related questions on Chegg. (Chegg Expert)

EXTRA CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

- Organized College Level Volleyball competition.
- Played for Nationals and Intercollege Volleyball tournaments.

Date: Signature